[Music]
[音乐]
so I guess we have to start because this
所以我想我们必须开始，因为这
is exactly the right time they want to
正是他们想要的正确时间
start at the right time and welcome
在合适的时间开始并欢迎
everyone to the session which is about
参加会议的所有人
how to build reaction server engine in
如何在其中构建反应服务器引擎
order to save your time because before
为了节省您的时间，因为之前
any other preparation and intro to you
其他准备和介绍
what we are going to do I want to save
我要保存什么
your time because I want to let you know
你的时间，因为我想让你知道
let you learn as much as possible that's
让您尽可能多地学习
why I want to share a little bit for
为什么我要分享一点
whom this talk so you will be able to go
谁在说这话，你就可以去
to another room or to another session
到另一个房间或另一个会话
and learn something better so this talk
并学到更好的东西
is for people who want to learn how new
适用于想要学习新知识的人
works and learn more a little bit about
工作，并了解更多有关
new kind of GDK near the lowest level of
最低水平的新型GDK
integration with non-blocking i/o if you
与非阻塞I / O集成，如果您
want to learn a little bit about project
想了解一些有关项目的信息
reactor in action this also be kind of
反应堆在行动这也是
really useful to you because we are
对您真的有用，因为我们
going to we are going to discuss a
去我们要讨论一个
little bit about some operators in
关于一些运营商的一点点
project reactor and of course if you
项目反应堆，当然，如果您
want to understand how reactive approach
想了解反应式方法
feeds to the server-side engine on the
饲料到服务器端引擎
lower on the lowest layer then this will
较低的最低层，那么这将
be also really useful to you so if you
对您也真的很有用，所以如果您
are still with me then let's let's go
仍然和我在一起然后我们走吧
and let me introduce myself that my name
让我自我介绍一下我的名字
is Alec I'm from Ukraine from from Kiev
是亚历克（Alec）我来自乌克兰，来自基辅
I work for a net if I company where we
如果我在哪里工作，我会为网工作
are building amazing product call it our
正在建立惊人的产品，称之为我们的
socket the next session will be
套接字下一个会话将是
dedicated to that to that product and
致力于该产品并
actually I am contributor to project
实际上我是项目的贡献者
reactors so I know everything about how
反应堆，所以我知道一切
it's going on inside reactor and how it
它在反应堆内部进行的过程
works etc so if you have n equation just
等等，所以如果你只有n个方程
with me and also I am organizing some
和我在一起，我也在组织一些
conferences in Ukraine so if you want to
会议在乌克兰，所以如果你想
learn and go to learn technology is
学习和去学习技术是
related to Java and enjoy Kiev and
与Java有关并喜欢Kiev和
Ukraine please come to those conferences
乌克兰请参加那些会议
or ping me I'll share some some
或ping我，我会分享一些
discounts to you all right I also wrote
打折给你好吧我也写过
a book related to reactive programming
与反应式编程有关的书
speed in spring but this is a little bit
春天的速度，但这有点
of marketing and now our main goal our
营销，现在我们的主要目标是
agenda so we will start with
议程，所以我们将从
understanding what we wanna see as a
理解我们想要看到的
reactive server
反应服务器
that will be the beginning then why do
那将是开始，然后为什么
we need tractor server engine or why for
我们需要拖拉机服务器引擎，或者为什么
example existing blocking technology
现有阻塞技术示例
doesn't feel real world's problems and
感觉不到现实世界的问题，
finally we will do some live coding on
最后，我们将对
implementing reactive server engine
实现反应式服务器引擎
that's our plan all right sounds good
那是我们的计划，听起来不错
great so let's go first of all what we
太好了，让我们首先开始
want to see under a reactive server
想在反应式服务器下看到
engine we want to see server this is the
我们要查看服务器的引擎，这是
main the main part of our of our
主要我们的主要部分
implementation and that server should be
实施，该服务器应该是
able to accept connection and we have to
能够接受连接，我们必须
provide some some ability to handle
提供一些处理能力
those quite so those connections using
那些非常，这样的连接使用
for example reactive programming model
例如反应式编程模型
this is an important part then what we
这是重要的部分，然后我们
want to have you want to have some pool
想要拥有一些泳池
of workers or pool of threads which will
工人或线程池将
be attached to every new connection and
附加到每个新连接，并
this connection will share for example
例如，此连接将共享
few valuable workers and then once it
几个有价值的工人，然后一旦
happens we want to have some but
碰巧我们想要一些但是
pressure control because this is
压力控制，因为这是
important reactive programming this is
重要的反应式编程，这是
about and reactive streams is about back
约和反应流约回来
pressure control and we want to preserve
压力控制，我们要保留
our resource in kind of in a normal
我们的资源在正常情况下
state and keep application just working
陈述并保持应用程序正常运行
that's why we want to control but prayer
这就是为什么我们要控制但祈祷
in the way if we want if we can't write
如果我们想要，如果我们不能写
something to to our output to our
对我们的输出到我们的东西
connections then we can ask for for new
连接，然后我们可以要求新的
date and not other way so once we
日期，而不是其他方式，所以一旦我们
receive for example but pressure request
例如接收但压力请求
or flow control or past for example give
或流程控制或过去例如
me a few more by it the server will
我还会再给我几个服务器
start send in our data we will apply
开始发送我们的数据，我们将适用
some transformation to it to them and
给他们一些转变，
send back that's what we want to have in
发回我们想要的东西
our reactive server engine from the code
代码中的反应式服务器引擎
perspective it could like it could look
透视它可能看起来像
like that so in a few words we want to
这样，我们想用几句话
accept or we want to create our server
接受或我们要创建服务器
by defining the host and port like that
通过这样定义主机和端口
then we want to define our kind of
那么我们想定义我们的
connection handler in this way this is
这样的连接处理程序是
pretty similar maybe if you attend that
如果你参加那很相似
r2 DBC talk you saw something similar
r2 DBC谈话，您看到了类似的内容
because this is a common pattern for
因为这是一种常见的模式
handle new connections and then we want
处理新的连接，然后我们想要
to have kind of
有种
straightforward way to read some data
读取某些数据的直接方法
from this connection using for example
从此连接使用例如
receive method and to send some data
接收方法并发送一些数据
back using a common common name add
返回使用共同的通用名称添加
methods and in both cases it will be
方法，在两种情况下都是
reactive streams we want a use project
我们想要使用项目的反应流
to act on it because it's a common way
采取行动，因为这是一种常见的方式
to to send some died to sent and protest
送一些死去送抗议
some data in reactive fashion but how
反应性的一些数据，但是如何
many of you are familiar with project
你们中的许多人都熟悉项目
factor used it before okay a few hands
几手之前就用过它
have you ever heard about Eric's Java
您是否听说过Eric的Java
maybe before or use it so I guess the
也许之前或使用它，所以我猜
same people all right so a little bit of
同一个人没事，所以一点点
you heard about that project it's
你听说过那个项目
basically about reactive programming and
基本上是关于反应式编程
reactive streams pretention so we want
反应流保持，所以我们想要
to use it in this way and of course in
以这种方式使用它，当然
order to start this engine you want to
为了启动这个引擎你想
call start and of course to keep main
呼叫开始，当然要保持主要
thread running we want to block the
线程正在运行，我们要阻止
whole execution in a few words
几句话就说明整个执行过程
everything is written in reactive
一切都写成反应式
fashion as you can see the main question
正如您所看到的主要问题
that you should ask me why do we need
你应该问我为什么我们需要
that why do we need reactive server
那为什么我们需要反应式服务器
engine in order to demonstrate that or
引擎以证明这一点或
in order to show why we do we need I'm
为了表明我们为什么要做，我们需要
going to show you why what's wrong with
将向您展示为什么出了什么问题
blocking i/o so let's do some small demo
阻止I / O，让我们做一些小演示
in order to understand what's wrong with
为了了解什么是错
blocking a young dot proposed I'm going
阻止一个小点提议我要去
to run plain socket server so this is a
运行普通套接字服务器，所以这是一个
simplest lowest layer implementation of
最简单的最低层实现
socket server which simply starts on
套接字服务器，仅在以下位置启动
port 8080 except connections this is a
端口8080，除了连接，这是一个
normal way to accept connection and to
接受连接的常规方法
process data in in lowest in GDK I all
在GDK中以最低的价格处理数据
on the GDK level so what we want to have
在GDK级别上，所以我们想要拥有
we want a SAP connection we want to read
我们想要一个我们想要阅读的SAP连接
some data from the input stream and we
输入流中的一些数据，我们
want to protest some lines by saying in
想通过说一些来抗议
echo message back so let's just start
回显消息，所以让我们开始吧
this plain application and let's see how
这个简单的应用程序，让我们看看如何
it works so it started yeah if you
它起作用了，所以它开始是的，如果你
notice in order to run every single to
通知以便运行每个
start everything really quickly I use
我使用时真的很快开始一切
growl here because growl is about quick
在这里咆哮，因为咆哮快了
startup and quick data processing so I'm
启动和快速数据处理，所以我
using it here and now let's connect to
在这里使用它，现在让我们连接到
my application using telnet so I can
我的应用程序使用telnet，因此我可以
and now I can write hello world and I
现在我可以写你好世界了
got a hello and a message do you see it
打个招呼，有消息你看到吗
I got echo message so basically it works
我收到回显消息，因此基本上可以正常工作
so I'm going I am able to write some
所以我要去写一些
data and observe some echo responds back
数据并观察到一些回声
so in general it horse so what's wrong
所以总的来说，这是怎么回事
is that first of all when I try to open
首先是当我尝试打开
another connection not kill Java but
另一个连接不是杀死Java，而是
open other connection nothing will
打开其他连接什么也不会
happen
发生
nothing will happen because do you think
什么都不会发生，因为你认为
that do you know the answer when nothing
那你什么都不知道的答案
happens the answer is really simple we
发生的答案很简单，我们
have only one thread which protests
只有一个线程抗议
protests data and if this thread is kind
抗议数据，并且该线程是否友好
of occupied by previous connection and
先前连接所占用的
it's occupied by previous connection the
它被先前的连接占用
new one won't be able to start kind of
新的将无法开始
processed data this that's why it's a
处理数据，这就是为什么它是
little bit of problem of course of this
当然有一点问题
solution for that we'll be creating some
为此，我们将创建一些解决方案
thread pool like that so this is a
这样的线程池，所以这是一个
normal way to create thread pool use for
创建用于的线程池的常规方法
example in that case our few available
在这种情况下的例子
processors in on my machine for demo
我机器上的处理器用于演示
purpose let's just put for example four
目的，让我们举四个例子
threads to process all the data and
线程来处理所有数据并
let's replace this plain connection
让我们替换这个简单的连接
logic is the same but ran executed on
逻辑是相同的，但是在
the thread form so the main difference
螺纹形式的主要区别
is now that once I accepted the
现在，一旦我接受了
connection
连接
I wanna execute it on put specific
我想具体执行
thread pool or on specific thread it
线程池或在特定线程上
clear okay so this is the simplest the
清楚好吧，这是最简单的
main logic is pretty similar so once I
主要逻辑非常相似，所以一旦我
protest everything the connection will
抗议一切联系
be freed so let's restart and let's see
被释放，让我们重新启动，让我们看看
whether it works or not so let's connect
无论是否有效，让我们连接
yes this works let's connect again this
是的，这有效，让我们再次连接
works again cool better at least so
至少可以再凉爽
let's not kill Java but works so another
让我们不要杀死Java，但可以这样工作
one not kill Java
一个不杀死Java的人
please save Java yes
请保存Java是
and this one works great so seems like
而且这个效果很好，看起来像
it's fine but what about another one
很好，但是另一个呢
connection oh this one doesn't work
连接哦，这个不起作用
because we exhausted all the the thread
因为我们耗尽了所有线程
pool and we don't have any available
池，我们没有任何可用
threads to process data and if you if we
处理数据的线程，如果您愿意，
are going to stop this program or pues
将要停止该程序或操作
it we will see that we have some task in
它会看到我们有一些任务
the queue and if we will try to open
队列，如果我们尝试打开
more connection eventually we will get Q
更多的连接最终我们将获得Q
out of size exception or something like
超出尺寸异常或类似
that which means that we don't have any
那意味着我们没有任何
available threads and memory in the or
或中的可用线程和内存
space in the queue so another obvious
队列中的空间，所以另一个明显
solution to that you'll be providing
您将提供的解决方案
what what we do when we want to handle
当我们想要处理时我们做什么
lots of lots of requests locking
很多请求锁定
requests scheduled it on cache it thread
请求将其安排在缓存线程上
pool right why not to use for example
池权为什么不使用例如
cache thread pool in order to handle all
缓存线程池以便处理所有
connections because as you might note I
连接，因为您可能会注意到我
know the cached read pool allows you to
知道缓存的读取池使您能够
create as many threads as you want right
根据需要创建尽可能多的线程
so let's try this and see what happened
所以让我们尝试一下，看看发生了什么
of course in this case we will have lots
当然在这种情况下，我们会有很多
of threads and we will be able to open
的线程，我们将能够打开
as many connections as we want but we
尽可能多的连接，但是我们
won't try to reproduce these using my
不会尝试使用我的
console in my terminal in order to test
在我的终端中进行控制台以进行测试
how resilient such application could be
这样的应用程序可能具有多大的弹性
I created a small evil dosser I called
我创造了一个小恶魔剂量药
this small application door sir and what
这个小应用门先生，还有什么
this application does is basically open
该应用程序基本上是打开的
ten thousand of connections and tried to
万个连接，并试图
spam my server with as many data as it
用尽可能多的数据向我的服务器发送垃圾邮件
had as it can so the simplest let's just
拥有它，所以最简单的就是
try whether it can yeah I guess it works
尝试是否可以，我猜它可行
so let's just try to run my app and see
因此，让我们尝试运行我的应用并查看
whether my main server implemented in
我的主服务器是否在
such way could survive or not so for
这样的方式可以生存或不生存
some reason it stopped what do you think
由于某种原因它停止了您的想法
what happened your idea
你的主意发生了什么
right we got out of memory because
对，我们走出了记忆，因为
threat is somewhat really expensive in
威胁在某些方面确实非常昂贵
Java it takes usually one megabyte of
Java通常需要一兆字节的
your memory and it's really it's really
你的记忆，真的，真的
expensive for for just running
跑步很贵
everything on new on new thread that's
在新线程上的所有内容都是
why it's a really bad connection model
为什么这是一个非常糟糕的连接模型
really bad kind of processing model to
真的很糟糕的处理模型
have one thread per connection and
每个连接只有一个线程，并且
that's why blocking could not survive
这就是为什么阻止无法生存
either you have to limit your number of
要么你必须限制你的数量
threads and in that case limit of number
线程，在这种情况下，数量限制
of simultaneous connection processed by
的同时连接的处理数量
your by your server or you have to
您的服务器旁边，或者您必须
handle lots of threads and that's why
处理很多线程，这就是为什么
you have to kind of pay lots of money
你必须要付出很多钱
for really huge machine with huge amount
对于数量巨大的真正大型机器
of memory and huge amount of processors
的内存和大量的处理器
that's why blocking is not good so let's
这就是为什么阻止效果不好，所以让我们
back to our slides and let's try to do
回到我们的幻灯片，让我们尝试做
some summary to see some drawbacks of
一些总结，看看一些缺点
blocking i/o
阻止I / O
first of all it's an efficient resource
首先，这是一种有效的资源
usage because you have to spit in case
用法，因为你必须吐以防万一
of thread per connection model that will
每个连接模型的线程数
take lots of memory increase it will
需要大量的内存增加
increase latency because in in this case
增加延迟，因为在这种情况下
you you want to kind of process you want
您想要一种想要的过程
to protest something in the really
抗议真正的事情
concurrent environment it will be hardly
并发环境几乎不会
possible to to manage some to really it
可能真正做到一些
schedule everything properly that's why
正确安排一切，这就是为什么
11c will significantly increase and
11c将显着增加，
finally it's easy to do such such
最终，这样做很容易
application because some someone can
申请，因为有人可以
kind of understand how many memory
了解多少内存
allocated for your app and doing some
为您的应用分配并做一些
such things like long live at connection
这样的事情像万岁连接
it can crush that person can really do -
它会粉碎一个人真正能够做到的-
your servers so that's why we need
您的服务器，这就是为什么我们需要
non-blocking i/o so let's try to
非阻塞I / O，让我们尝试
understand what not blocking i/o and
了解什么不阻止I / O和
count on blocking i/o looks like so
依靠阻止I / O看起来像这样
first of all in non-blocking i/o the
首先在非阻塞I / O
main the essential part of everything is
最主要的是一切
server socket channel server socket
服务器套接字通道服务器套接字
channel has another kind of culture part
频道还有另一种文化成分
or part of non-blocking execution which
或非阻塞执行的一部分
is called selector so using selector you
被称为选择器，所以使用选择器
can start listening to for example
例如可以开始听
incoming can
进来的罐头
action for example using operation
动作，例如使用操作
except so once you've got a new
除非如此，一旦您有了新的
connection the server channel will
连接服务器通道将
mattify about new user or new connection
关于新用户或新连接的问题
open it in a few words so what next once
用几句话打开它，接下来一次
you got a new connection to your server
您与服务器建立了新连接
you have to listen to some data right
你必须听一些数据
but what I want to kind of emphasize
但我想强调的是
here you can't just say to server
在这里你不能只对服务器说
service the server socket Channel now I
现在服务服务器套接字通道
want to listen to operation reads now
想听操作现在读
you have to go to connection use the
你必须去连接使用
same selector but now you have this to
相同的选择器，但现在您有了
register this selector to this socket
将此选择器注册到此套接字
Channel this house socket of your works
引导您的作品的这个房屋插座
you can't just use the same place to do
你不能只在同一个地方做
everything you have to split you have to
您必须拆分的所有内容
do more movements and more exercises in
做更多的动作和更多的锻炼
order to start listening to particular
为了开始听特定的
events from this connection and this
此连接和此事件
kind of not good design from SS for me
SS对我来说不是很好的设计
all right but what next
好的，但是接下来呢
all right suppose you got some few bytes
好吧，假设您有一些字节
of data of course you want to start
当然要开始的数据
reading them right that's usual
正常阅读它们
operation so you want to start
操作，所以你想开始
processing date those data you protest
处理您抗议的数据的日期
them and you want to write them back
他们，你想写回去
right that's usual operation or
对，这是通常的操作，或者
operational flow so you want to send
操作流程，因此您想发送
those data back but what can happen it
这些数据返回，但会发生什么
can happen that only one part of the
可能会发生，只有一部分
data could be written to sake channel
数据可以写入清酒通道
because in non-blocking world there is
因为在非阻塞世界中
not warranties that connection is TCP
不保证连接是TCP
connection can handle all the data
连接可以处理所有数据
that's why it's not blocking in case for
这就是为什么它不会阻止以防万一
example you just wrote only one part of
例如，您只写了一部分
your your byte buffer for example you
您的字节缓冲区，例如您
have to store this byte buffers to
必须将此字节缓冲区存储到
somewhere and then you have to listen to
某个地方，然后你必须听
another type of operations related to
另一类与
write and in that case socket channel
写，在这种情况下，套接字通道
will notify you once it has valuable
一旦有价值就将通知您
kind of space to write some data to do
一种空间来写一些数据来做
it again
再来一次
it will notify about write operations
它将通知有关写操作
and then only after that you will be
然后只有在那之后
able to try to write it again so this is
能够尝试再次编写它，所以这是
the main flow of non-blocking
非阻塞的主要流程
interaction this kind of here
互动在这里
how it looks like from the code
从代码看起来如何
perspective this is basically the main
观点，这基本上是主要的
setup of a non-blocking server first of
首先设置非阻塞服务器
all you have to create an open socket
创建开放式套接字所需要做的一切
channel being it to specific address
通道到特定地址
similarly to just blocking i/o but the
类似于阻止I / O，但是
important part that you have to say this
重要的部分，你必须这样说
is non blocking communication so you
没有阻碍交流，所以您
have to configure non blocking
必须配置非阻塞
explicitly this is another drawback then
显然，这是另一个缺点
you have to open selector this is
您必须打开选择器，这是
another part you have to start listening
另一部分，你必须开始听
for example on the sap demand and then
例如在汁液需求上，然后
you have to loop over it
你必须遍历它
of course this part you will block your
当然这部分你会阻止
loop execution it won't just spin your
循环执行不仅会旋转您的
CPU but it will block until new
CPU，但会一直阻塞直到新
connection so once you got me a
连接，所以一旦你给我一个
connection selector will execute the
连接选择器将执行
code inside it and then you will be able
里面的代码，然后您将能够
to do some actions ok let's try to see
做一些动作好吧，让我们尝试看看
what we can do inside this once we got
一旦获得，我们可以在其中做什么
new connection for example the set new
新连接，例如设置新
connection we have to say except we have
联系我们不得不说，除了
to configure it in non-blocking fashion
以非阻塞方式配置它
again and then we have to put it in some
再一次，然后我们必须把它放在一些
collection because there is no other way
收集，因为没有其他方法
to store the connections we have to do
存储我们必须做的连接
manage them ourselves and this is
自己管理他们，这是
another challenge that happens is
发生的另一个挑战是
non-blocking hang up finally we have to
无阻塞挂断最后我们要
register that you are ready you have to
注册您已经准备好
show you intent that you are ready to
向您表明您已准备好
read some data from this connection and
从此连接读取一些数据，然后
only after that you will be able for
只有在那之后你才能
example to start process the data this
这个例子开始处理数据
is another part this is a part related
是另一部分，这是相关的一部分
to data reading so once you get a
进行数据读取，因此一旦获得
notification about available data you
关于您可用数据的通知
have to again get the channel allocate
必须再次获得频道分配
some buffer for reading the data and of
一些缓冲区，用于读取数据和
course put the day to put the buffer
当然要放一天缓冲
somewhere because for now it's unclear
某个地方，因为目前尚不清楚
how to send those buffers those data to
如何将那些缓冲区发送到这些数据
for example user logic because what we
例如用户逻辑，因为我们
want to build you want to build some
要建立你想建立一些
some normal server which allows everyone
一些普通的服务器，它允许每个人
to put a list node put a listener and
放置一个列表节点，放置一个侦听器，
then protest every every byte buffer
然后抗议每个字节缓冲区
that came from from the connection and
来自连接和
how to do that in this model it's
如何在这个模型中做到这一点
another challenge actually I don't know
我不知道的另一个挑战
how to - man that correctly because this
如何-正确地解决这个问题，因为
requires to use
需要使用
perative programming because pronounce
定性编程，因为发音
everything is in imperative programming
一切都在命令式编程中
and it could be little and often clear
它可能很少而且经常很清楚
as for me and finally once we wrote once
至于我，最后一次，我们写了一次
we read some data from from the
我们从
connection you want to say okay let me
你想说的联系好吧让我
know when I can write some data back due
知道什么时候可以回写一些数据
to this channel and once we get another
到这个频道，一旦我们得到另一个
K notification we will be able to start
K通知，我们将可以开始
writing data to the channel yes we have
将数据写入通道是的，我们有
to define our view associated with this
定义与此相关的视图
channel and that we will then we will
渠道，然后我们将
have to to iterative live write this
不得不迭代地活写这个
data back to the channel so this is
数据返回到通道，所以这是
basically what happens with such
基本上这样会发生什么
execution after all once you've wrote
写完之后执行
everything you've had you have to say
你所拥有的一切，你不得不说
again I will no listen to read data and
同样，我不会听数据
this is basically their fourth workflow
这基本上是他们的第四个工作流程
in non-blocking i/o do you think it's a
在非阻塞I / O中，您认为这是一个
little bit complex do you agree with
你同意一点点复杂
that yes this is really complex and I
是的，这真的很复杂，我
actually don't want to kind of tackle
其实不想解决
all of this infrastructural code so
所有这些基础架构代码
let's summarize where is the complexity
让我们总结一下复杂性在哪里
here first of all Neil in general is
首先，尼尔一般是
really complex is it designed to not the
它真的设计得很复杂
kind of regular developers and only kind
那种普通的开发商，只有那种
of abnormal people can can work with
可以与异常人一起工作
that without any problems then selector
没有任何问题的选择器
and data is absolutely unrelated in case
和数据绝对无关
you want to handle your data you have to
您想要处理数据，您必须
do lots of movement and exercises to
做很多运动和锻炼来
make it correctly and it's easy to shoot
使其正确且易于拍摄
yourself in the leg that's why it's yeah
你自己在腿上，这就是为什么
complex another point of complexity and
另一个复杂点
yeah reason right is also complex
是的，正确的理由也很复杂
operation and because you have to count
操作，因为你必须数
that everything is done blocking all
一切都完成了
right so let's now talk how to implement
好的，现在让我们谈谈如何实施
that design that I mentioned at the very
我刚才提到的那个设计
beginning how to create this beautiful
开始如何创造这个美丽
functional and reactive solution on top
功能和反应性解决方案位于顶部
of our functional reactive new
我们的功能性反应新
implementation or API on top of that
实施或API之上
first of all we have to care about back
首先我们要关心回来
pressure and what we want to have we
压力和我们想要拥有的
want to yeah we want to have some
想要，我们想要一些
multi-threading
多线程
and of course in previous solution this
当然在先前的解决方案中
is this will be hardly hardly handle it
难道这很难解决吗
in general once you start working that
一般来说，一旦您开始工作
you will like homer in front of reactive
你会喜欢在反应堆前面的荷马
Factory
厂
alright in general three is a good good
好吧，总的来说三好
portent good word from well-known guy to
向知名人士传达好词，
say don't vote from from complexity run
说不要从复杂性运行中投票
from it right so if you wanna we want to
从它开始，所以如果您想我们想要
vote from it want to run away from it
从中投票要逃避
this way let's run from it let's run to
这样我们就可以开始运行了
react two streams and let's try to
反应两个流，让我们尝试
implement everything using a synchronous
使用同步来实现一切
non blocking Pro and of streaming
非阻塞专业和流
because reactor seems is about it and
因为反应堆似乎就是这样
streaming model is somewhat natural to
流模型对于
Taniya because what you do you read
谷屋，因为你读什么
bytes from connection and connection in
来自连接和连接中的字节
general is a stream of bytes right so it
general是正确的字节流，所以它
naturally feeds each other so let's try
自然地互相喂食，让我们尝试
to do that because also reactive streams
这样做是因为反应性流
provide us with building back pressure
给我们增加背压
in turn which one we are going to use
反过来，我们将使用哪一个
project factor because project tractor
项目因素，因为项目拖拉机
is a superset on reg 10 over on
是第10条的超集
directive streams libraries this
指令流库this
implementation it provides us with
为我们提供的实现
extensive set of operators and it has
大量的运营商，它具有
built in model for really useful and
内置模型非常有用并且
simple manipulation by trans so let's do
通过trans进行简单操作，让我们开始
it let's call it finally and let's go to
最后让我们称之为它，然后转到
to our code let's kill Java first of all
我们的代码让我们首先杀死Java
this is important to kill Java before
这对于杀死Java很重要
before anything so let me close it and
在任何事情之前，让我关闭它，
say kill Java great I kill Java and now
说杀死Java很棒我杀死Java现在
let's try to rewrite this guy let's
让我们尝试重写这个家伙，让我们
first start with our reactive API what
首先从我们的反应式API开始
we want to achieve we wanna write what
我们想要实现我们想要写什么
every after every iteration we will try
每次迭代之后，我们都会尝试
to run this piece of code and we will
运行这段代码，我们将
try to figure out whether it works or
尝试找出它是否有效或
not
不
okay doesn't make sense hope it does so
好吧，希望这样做没有道理
here is there is here is just essential
这里是这里，只是必不可少的
implementation of this is just an API I
这只是API的实现
would say of our reactive server under
会说我们的反应式服务器
the hood we don't have anything so if
引擎盖我们什么都没有，所以如果
you're going
你要去
this is implementation we will see empty
这是实现，我们将看到空的
empty kind of implementation and from
空的实现和
that point we are going to we will start
我们将要开始的那一点
implementing everything so in order to
实施一切，以便
since we have everything reactive and we
因为我们所有的东西都是反应性的，所以我们
have to return our kind of server we
必须返回我们的那种服务器
have to make a startup of the server or
必须启动服务器或
synchronous we have to to write every
同步，我们必须写每个
say everything in the synchronous
在同步中说出一切
fashion and that's why I'm going to do
时尚，这就是为什么我要去做
start with writing not that one but this
从写那个不是那个开始
is a few startup actions so what what do
是一些启动操作，所以该怎么办
we do here first of all we've wrote a
我们首先在这里做，我们写了一个
convenient way to to listen to some
听一些方便的方法
subscribers so we want to create some
订户，所以我们想创建一些
source of data in that case which will
在这种情况下的数据源
push new connections to downstream of
将新的连接推送到下游
course we will ignore them because it
当然我们会忽略他们，因为
doesn't it's not important to first our
是不是首先我们不重要
top but that's how we start then what we
顶部，但这就是我们开始的方式，然后我们
want to have you want to have we want to
想要拥有你想要拥有我们想要
run our kind of main business logic
运行我们的主要业务逻辑
hidden inside our push or inside our
隐藏在我们的推送或我们的内部
kind of source on a different thread for
在不同线程上的一种来源
to do that we create another scheduler
为此，我们创建另一个调度程序
so scheduler is a part of project
所以调度程序是项目的一部分
reactor which allows us to create a
反应堆，使我们能够创建一个
thread pool ok the thread pool on which
好的线程池
this part of the logic will ran will be
这部分逻辑将运行将
ran is it clear ok then we just ignore
跑得好吗，然后我们就忽略了
everything and convert our flux to come
一切并转换我们的通量来
on and that's it the next step will be
继续，下一步就是
writing and implementing of course some
当然写和执行一些
plain neo interaction so to start
普通的新互动，因此开始
working this new you have to just to
工作这个新的，你只需要
just stop a few lines of code like that
像这样停止几行代码
so really easy right yeah I decided to
真的很容易，是的，我决定
simplify and to sacrifice explain and
简化并牺牲解释和
write and everything by myself
我自己写东西
so I'm going to explain what's going on
所以我要解释发生了什么
here is the same as you have seen on the
这与您在
slides
滑梯
this is startup of socket channel here I
这是套接字通道的启动
mark it as non-blocking
将其标记为非阻塞
then I open selector in order to listen
然后我打开选择器以听
to you to action specified by this
给您执行此操作
selector key and then I do some actions
选择器键，然后执行一些操作
in order to to listen for example to
为了听例如
cancellation of the stream so there is a
取消流，所以有一个
convenient way to to listen
方便的聆听方式
cancellation which is synced on disposed
在处置时同步的取消
handler and in that way once I got
处理程序，以这种方式，一旦我得到
cancellation actually I will just close
取消实际上我只会关闭
my server and that's it then we have the
我的服务器，就是这样，我们有了
loop which will be running until
循环将一直运行到
something is cancelled and here is the
某些东西被取消了，这是
selection that you have seen before
您以前见过的选择
right identical code now we are going to
正确的代码，现在我们要
just try to implement part of the logic
只是尝试实现部分逻辑
here but we have to understand what do
在这里，但我们必须了解做什么
we want to have here here we just want
我们想在这里有我们只想
we have B in this by this action we
通过这个动作我们在这个B
simply accept the new connection right
只需接受新的连接权限
so this guy returned as another socket
所以这个家伙又回到了另一个插座
channel which represent the connection
表示连接的通道
between between our client and what we
在我们的客户和我们之间
handle it on the server side here we
我们在服务器端处理它
mark it as non blocking now we have
现在将其标记为非阻塞
another kind of representation or
另一种表示形式或
implementation around it which you
围绕它的实现
provide us with reactive API and that
为我们提供反应式API，
should sound some somewhat like
应该听起来有点像
connection right you wanna some some
连接权，你想一些
wrapper around socket channel which will
套接字通道周围的包装器将
be named as connection so here I have
被命名为连接，所以我在这里
this interface colored connection which
该接口有色连接
has only two methods which I mentioned
我只提到了两种方法
on the slides the first one allows us to
在幻灯片上，第一个允许我们
to listen to increment by buffers right
聆听缓冲区的增量
and the second one will simply allows us
第二个将简单地允许我们
to send those data back to the stream is
将那些数据发送回流是
it clear
很清楚
simply simple interface so let's go to
简单的界面，让我们转到
the implementation this is placeholder
占位符的实现
class for that which doesn't have any
没有任何东西的类
implementation so far and from that
到目前为止的实现
point we are going to implement the rest
点，我们将执行其余的
of the sync so first of all we have to
同步，所以首先我们必须
give a little bit of data or information
提供一点数据或信息
to this connection about outside world
关于外界的这种联系
first of all what what verse to mention
首先要提什么经文
is that connection will be kind of
是那种联系会是
you'll be responsible for data reading
您将负责数据读取
and date of writing and we don't want to
和写作日期，我们不想
move this responsibility to to the main
将此责任转移到主要
server engine because it will just
服务器引擎，因为它将
confuse every single these allow us to
这些让我们感到困惑的每一个
to work easily with this with this code
与此代码一起轻松使用
that's why we are going to do ask main
这就是为什么我们要问主要
server for some kind of main required
服务器需要某种主要的
fields for example for for some fields
例如某些领域的领域
related to socket channel so we will ask
与套接字通道有关，所以我们会问
for connect
用于连接
or actual representation of circuit
或电路的实际表示
channel from GDK neo and also we are
来自GDK neo的频道，我们也是
going to to ask in order to kind of
要问，以便那种
decouple the server engine and our kind
分离服务器引擎和我们的引擎
of or source of selection from our
从我们的选择或选择的来源
connection we want to have some
连接我们想要一些
notifications or way to to listen to
通知或聆听方式
some new notifications or actions from
来自的一些新通知或操作
the main engine and since this is kind
主机，因为这是善良的
of stream of updates we can use the same
我们可以使用相同的更新流
kind of programming model using project
使用项目的一种编程模型
using project reactor and basically when
使用项目反应堆，基本上什么时候
we want to listen to you for example to
我们想听听你的声音，例如
read updates or to the ability to read
阅读更新或阅读能力
from the connection we want to subscribe
从我们要订阅的连接
to some stream of data right the same
对某些数据流相同
for writes if you want to read too if
如果您也想阅读的话
you want to listen to some writes
你想听一些写
updates or for some notification that we
更新或关于我们的一些通知
can write data to you due to the
可以向您写入数据
connection you want to listen to floods
你想听洪水的连接
of another sexual selection keys that's
另一个性选择键的
what we want to have and here some
我们想要拥有什么，这里有一些
basics construction of this this this
这个这个的基础建设
part we don't want to dig into this
部分我们不想深入探讨
deeper but now what we want to try to
更深入，但现在我们想尝试
implement is receiving and send in logic
工具正在接收和发送逻辑
in order to receive data we have to
为了接收数据，我们必须
listen to read notify - - and read kind
听阅读通知--和阅读种类
of notifications right so once we got
正确的通知，所以一旦我们得到
the notifications that we can read
我们可以阅读的通知
something from this from from the
从这个东西
connection we should start read from it
连接，我们应该从中读取
and basically we have to use our reading
基本上我们必须使用我们的阅读
at the fire in order to start listening
在火上开始听
on the other hand to start listening for
另一方面开始听
read events we have to register kind of
阅读事件，我们必须注册某种
listener right we have to remember that
听众，我们必须记住
part that they have shown you on the
他们已经在
slides related to to the two Z's let me
与两个Z有关的幻灯片让我
show you this again in order to get new
再次向您展示以获取新的
updates you have to define to see it you
您必须定义更新才能看到它
have to say I want to listen to read
不得不说我想听阅读
updates right but the main question
更新正确，但主要问题
since we have everything reactive and if
因为我们所有的东西都是反应性的，如果
we are going to take a look at our
我们将看看我们的
business logic and this business logic
业务逻辑和此业务逻辑
could be written in absolutely different
可以用完全不同的方式写
very mad
很生气
for example we can delay our
例如，我们可以延迟我们的
subscription we can do some synchronous
订阅我们可以做一些同步
action we can send we can create some
我们可以发送的动作我们可以创建一些
proxy server which will send data to
代理服务器将数据发送到
another server and of course we don't
另一个服务器，当然我们不
know when we get for example when the
知道我们什么时候得到例如
endpoint or consumer logic you'll be
端点或消费者逻辑
able to to start listening for the data
能够开始监听数据
that's why we don't want to start
这就是为什么我们不想开始
listening too early so we don't want to
听得太早了，所以我们不想
register too early for for incoming read
太早注册，无法读取
notifications and that's why we want a
通知，这就是为什么我们想要一个
register only and only when when the
仅当且仅当
kind of our business logic sent us a
我们的业务逻辑给我们带来了
subscription or notification that it's
订阅或通知
ready the convenient way to listen to
准备方便的聆听方式
you to that action is of course by doing
您采取这种行动当然是通过
by listening or by adding operator on
通过听或通过添加运算符
subscribe do unsubscribe and what it
订阅取消订阅及其内容
gives us so once someone subscriber to
给我们，所以一旦有人订阅
our kind of stream we are absolutely
我们绝对是
ready to start doing something and this
准备开始做某事，这
will be the main point and the main kind
将是重点和主要种类
of start point for our listening to to
我们聆听的起点
to read notifications so what we going
阅读通知，所以我们要去
what we are going to do we will try to
我们将要做的是
implement something like something like
实现类似的东西
that sorry we eat yeah receiver here we
抱歉，我们在这里吃了接收器，我们
go this is what we have to write first
去，这是我们首先要写的
of all we have to add a kind of handle
我们必须添加一种处理
for don't subscribe action so once we
因为不要订阅动作，所以一旦我们
get a subscriber we will try to find our
得到订户，我们将尝试找到我们的
selector and we are going to register
选择器，我们将要注册
our selector to our socket Channel and
我们的套接字通道的选择器和
in this way wake up the whole execution
这样就唤醒了整个执行过程
and say okay now we are ready to you to
说好吧，我们已经准备好向您
read data we are fine then in order to
读取数据我们可以，然后为了
keep the latest selection key because
保留最新的选择键，因为
this is important this is another trick
这很重要，这是另一个技巧
you can't use the same selection key
您不能使用相同的选择键
everywhere you have to listen to new
到处都必须听新歌
updates and in case you you will try to
更新，以防万一您将尝试
use the older one you will be able to to
使用较旧的
register in other events and this is
在其他事件中注册，这是
another problem this this neo so every
这个新人的另一个问题
every new update every new selection key
每次新更新每次新选择键
notification you have to store it in the
通知，您必须将其存储在
field of course this this part of the
当然，这部分
code allows us to clean up connection
代码允许我们清理连接
for example and cancellation action
例如取消动作
this is the main part of the logic which
这是逻辑的主要部分
allows us to read few bytes from the
允许我们从
channel tea seed and then in case we
引导茶种子，然后以防万一
have some data in the channel we will
通道中有一些数据，我们将
try to sand it I want to pay your
尝试打磨它，我想付你
attention that of course we could write
注意，我们当然可以写
something like that let me show you we
这样的事情让我告诉你我们
could write something like that it could
可以写像这样的东西
write something like that and of course
写这样的东西，当然
we can write something like like that
我们可以这样写
but I want to pay your attention that
但我想引起您的注意
now interactive streams is a lag oh you
现在交互式流是一个滞后哦
may try to do something like that but
可能会尝试这样做
once you get now return it to to your to
一旦获得，立即将其返回给您
your map operator we will get an
您的地图运营商，我们将获得
exception which will close your reactive
异常将关闭您的反应
streams it's important to remember that
记住重要的一点是
null is kind of forbidden result of
null是一种禁止的结果
mapping for example and you can't send
例如映射，您就无法发送
any announce to during your data
数据发布期间的任何公告
streaming that's important that's why
这很重要，这就是为什么
there is another can get convenient way
还有另一种可以方便的方法
implement it in handle operator and what
在句柄运算符中实现它以及什么
you have to do if you have some data it
如果有一些数据就必须要做
provides you with something let me just
为您提供一些让我满意的东西
replace lambda with an in anonymous
用in匿名替换lambda
class it provides you with synchronizing
它为您提供同步的类
and what you have to do during this
以及在此期间您需要做什么
execution you have to you have to either
执行，你必须要么
execute this sync this next or you can
接下来执行此同步，否则您可以
easily complete this execution by same
轻松完成同一执行
thing so you have kind of you can keep
东西，所以你有种可以保留的东西
hands on control of I've ever seen
掌握我所见过的一切
what's going on inside the stream this
流里面发生了什么
is important part and this allows us to
是重要的部分，这使我们能够
either send some data or just filter or
发送一些数据或只是过滤或
skip the event this is important part of
跳过事件，这是重要的部分
reactors that you have to remember all
你必须记住的反应堆
right let's go to data send and all we
好的，让我们去发送数据
have to do basically at the data
基本上要在数据上做
sentenced part you have to subscribe to
您必须订阅的被判刑部分
you to the stream because we wanna as I
您到小溪，因为我们想像我
mentioned we have to keep all the logic
提到我们必须保持所有逻辑
of reading and writing inside the
在里面阅读和写作
connection because connection is part is
连接，因为连接是一部分
responsible for all kind of interaction
负责各种互动
this is real connection
这是真正的联系
that's why we want to do all this action
这就是为什么我们要做所有这些事情
inside connection and of course we have
内部连接，当然我们有
to create subscriber but as you can see
创建订户，但如您所见
subscriber is a little bit of kind of we
订户是我们的一种
have to write a little bit of
必须写一点
implementation for that that's why we
这就是为什么实现
maybe want to use some convenient wait
也许想使用一些方便的等待
for project from project reactor reaches
用于项目反应堆到达的项目
base subscriber but in general I don't
基本订户，但总的来说我不
want to create another object because a
要创建另一个对象，因为
more object to you garbage collector
给您更多对象垃圾回收器
more the less performance you gain you
越多，获得的性能就越少
want to produce less object to you to
想要减少对您的对象
our environment that's why the more kind
这就是为什么我们的环境更加友善
of convenient way to do that is to just
方便的方法就是
extend a subscriber like this and to
扩展这样的订户并
implement this plain logic inside the
在内部实现这种简单的逻辑
same closet this won't be kind of
同一壁橱，这不会是
prohibited so what we want to have we
禁止，所以我们想要拥有我们
want to have byte buffer subscriber
想要拥有字节缓冲区订户
implemented here and we are looking for
在这里实施，我们正在寻找
two main methods required for our for
我们需要的两种主要方法
our implementations the first one is who
我们的实现第一个是谁
unsubscribe which allows us to override
退订，这使我们可以覆盖
kind of manipulation of under
对底层的一种操纵
subscription and use in subscription now
订阅并立即用于订阅
we can say how many objects or how many
我们可以说多少个对象或多少个
elements we are ready to read right this
我们准备好阅读的元素
is a way to to start control to start
是一种开始控制的方式
doing flow control between the upstream
在上游之间进行流量控制
and downstream and at this point to just
和下游，在这一点上，
start everything to just start
从头开始一切
executions we wanna request only one by
我们只想要求一个死刑犯
buffer from the connection and this will
从连接缓冲，这将
start our execution on the other hand we
另一方面，我们开始执行
want to listen to some incoming byte
想听一些传入的字节
buffer so we want to override who come
缓冲，所以我们想覆盖谁来
next you want to listen to you
接下来你想听你的
incoming buffer at what we want to do we
我们想要做什么的传入缓冲区
want to write some simple piece of code
想写一些简单的代码
like this not like this but like right
像这样不是像这样而是对的
you want to write some yeah simple piece
你想写一些简单的作品
of code like this which simply just
像这样的代码
write eight it to the circuit channel in
将其写入八个到电路通道
case we got some Putra Zulte which is -1
情况下，我们得到了一些-1
it means that something went from this
这意味着有些事情
our connection so we have to simply
我们的联系，所以我们只需要
cancel our execution
取消执行
and what do you want to have to do then
那你想做什么
in case everything is fine and we've
万一一切都很好，我们已经
wrote all the data we have to simply
写下了我们必须简单地完成的所有数据
request for another piece of nature
要求另一种自然
right this is the simplest execution
对，这是最简单的执行
flow you've wrote some date and we
你写了一些约会，我们
request it for another few bytes of data
请求它再获取几个字节的数据
and that's it
就是这样
of course there is a few corner cases
当然有一些极端的情况
here for example just imagine that you
例如，在这里想象一下你
were you were not able to to write
你不能写东西吗
everything at once in one connection and
一次连接一切
of course you have to store that by
当然，您必须将其存储
buffer because now we have to listen to
缓冲，因为现在我们必须听
write update so we have to store receive
写更新，所以我们必须存储接收
it by buffer to a field which is here so
通过缓冲区将其移至此处的字段
I hit him I hit it and now we have to
我打了他，我打了，现在我们必须
store it this by buffer here we have to
通过缓冲区将其存储在这里，我们必须
interact with selection key again and
再次与选择键进行交互，
define our intent to listen to write
定义我们的倾听意图
updates but now the question how we will
更新，但现在的问题是我们将如何
be notified about this write update we
收到有关此写入更新的通知，我们
have this stream of notification so we
有此通知流，所以我们
have to somehow use it we have to use it
必须以某种方式使用它，我们必须使用它
at the very beginning of execution and
在执行的开始
since very the very beginning of
从一开始
execution is of course unsubscribe
执行当然是退订的
method because once we got a
方法，因为一旦我们得到
subscription everything runtime has
订阅运行时具有的所有内容
started that's why we have to put
开始，这就是为什么我们必须把
interaction we is listening on write
我们正在听写的互动
updates here and it will could look like
在这里更新，它将看起来像
that so what we do what do we do
所以我们做什么我们做什么
basically here we listen for
基本上我们在这里听
notifications about right in that case
在这种情况下有关权利的通知
about right selection keys this will be
关于正确的选择键，这将是
right selection key and once we get it
正确的选择键，一旦我们得到它
we just simply have to say again now
我们现在只需要再说一次
just stop let you find me about fright
停下来让你找到我的恐惧
availability because in case you won't
可用性，因为万一您不会
do that it will just spin the processor
这样做只会旋转处理器
every every second by sending the I'm
每秒发送一次
ready to write I'm able to write some
准备写我可以写一些
data I'm able to write some data and
数据，我能够写一些数据，
this is some what we don't want to have
这是我们不想拥有的
here that's why we immediately once we
这就是为什么我们一旦
get a notification about read kind of
收到有关阅读类型的通知
write ability they say okay now we want
他们说的写能力好吧，现在我们要
to read listen to read don't let you
阅读听阅读不要让你
find me about writes updates and then
找到我关于写更新，然后
they have to still yeah this part should
他们必须仍然是，这部分应该
be hidden we will back to this too
隐藏起来，我们也会回到这个
later but basically what we have to do
稍后，但基本上我们要做的是
we have to send our kind of try we will
我们必须发送我们的尝试，我们将
send the same store at buffer previously
以前在缓冲区发送相同的存储
two to execution in the main logic that
二要执行的主要逻辑是
what we want to do afterwards so once we
之后我们要做什么，所以一旦我们
got a notification about fright ability
收到有关恐惧能力的通知
it means that we have some data to write
这意味着我们有一些数据要写
and we have to try to write them back
我们必须尝试将其写回
again and afterwards if everything is
一次又一次，如果一切都
successful we will request some for some
成功的我们将要求一些
new bytes from from in comment stream so
来自评论流中的新字节，因此
this is the whole execution model so
这是整个执行模型，所以
let's check whether yeah we have to just
让我们检查是否是
subscribe here we have to write few more
订阅这里，我们必须写一些
lines of code because everything should
代码行，因为一切都应该
be a synchronous and reactive so we have
成为同步和被动的，所以我们有
to start every scene only when someone
仅当有人时才开始每个场景
subscribe to our sand model so that's
订阅我们的沙子模型，所以
why we have to use from runnable we have
为什么我们必须使用可运行的
to do something like that and then we
做这样的事情，然后我们
have to open it after that we have to
必须打开它之后，我们必须
subscribe to to our data stream that's
订阅我们的数据流
how it should black should look like so
黑色应该看起来像这样
let's try to finalize everything let's
让我们尝试最终确定一切
try to put some piece of logic here so
尝试在这里放置一些逻辑
what we have to do right now we have to
我们现在必须要做的是
do some process kind of some
做一些过程
notification or stream for notification
通知或通知流
management so in order to provide our
管理，以便提供我们的
connection so here we have our double X
连接，所以在这里我们有我们的双X
connection here we have provided with
我们在这里提供的连接
some way to notify about with some kind
用某种方式通知
of implementation of streams for reads
读取流的实现方式
and writes and one of the option to
然后写入，其中之一是
manually so quite easy to the stream
手动，因此很容易流
because we want to manually push data to
因为我们要手动将数据推送到
the stream we want to basically use for
我们想要基本用于的流
example processors because processors is
示例处理器，因为处理器是
a parts of reactive streams
反应性流的一部分
specification it provides you
它为您提供的规格
implementation of us of protect of of
实施我们的保护
publisher and subscriber so basically
发布者和订阅者如此基本
what can downstream do it can subscribe
下游可以做什么？
to the stream and you what you can do
到小溪，你可以做什么
you can use for example methods like on
您可以使用示例方法，例如on
next in order to push data to to your
接下来为了将数据推送到您的
subscriber manually so this is a way to
手动订阅者，因此这是一种方法
do that and once we provided everything
做到这一点，一旦我们提供了一切
store at some
存放在一些
in the map which is required part of
在地图中这是必填部分
managing all the sinks because we have
管理所有汇，因为我们有
some somehow associate particular
以某种方式联想到特定
processors with particular kind of
具有特定种类的处理器
channel then we have to to listen to
频道，然后我们必须听
read
读
notifications and of course once we get
通知，当然，一旦我们得到
it we have to find out to which to which
我们必须找出到哪个
kind of which connection has those
那种联系有那些
processors and then we have to send a
处理器，然后我们必须发送一个
particular notification to this that
对此的特别通知
processor and of course we have to write
处理器，当然我们必须编写
absolutely identical logic for for right
正确的逻辑完全相同
in order to notify about writes updates
为了通知有关写入更新
or ability to write data to the channel
或将数据写入通道的能力
are you okay so far so good
到目前为止还好吗
is it clear a little bit too many
清楚一点吗
information and the standard but for now
信息和标准，但暂时
it's yeah of course this is a complex
是的，这当然很复杂
part but for now what we have to try to
部分，但现在我们必须尝试
do of course we have to try to run this
当然，我们必须尝试运行此
up and see whether it works or not right
起来看看它是否有效
in order to figure out whether we
为了弄清楚我们是否
brought something something
带些东西
understandable and more cobbler first of
首先可以理解和更多的补鞋匠
all so let's try to open a connection
因此，让我们尝试打开一个连接
yeah it seems that it works this piece
是的，这似乎很有效
of kind of little bit understandable
有点可以理解
code called Borges so let's write to to
称为Borges的代码，让我们写到
verify whether it's better than kind of
验证它是否比某种更好
block you know right this is the main
阻止，你知道这是主要的
idea too to show all these
展示所有这些的想法
demonstrations along the better API so
更好的API的演示
let's try to run our dosser and see
让我们尝试运行我们的剂量仪，看看
whether yeah it works but let's go - oh
是否可以，但我们走吧-哦
it this guy works that's great but we
这个家伙的作品很棒，但是我们
missed another point so in general it
错过了另一点，所以总的来说
works it allows us to to process all the
它可以使我们处理所有
data but now if you're going to look at
数据，但现在如果您要查看
our monitor in order to figure out how
我们的显示器，以找出如何
many processors are busy by doing some
许多处理器忙于做一些
work we have to see where is that where
工作，我们必须看到哪里在哪里
is my CPU here we go we will see that
是我的CPU在这里，我们将看到
only few processors will be busy first
只有很少的处理器会首先忙
of all because the whole implementation
毕竟是因为整个实施
of our business logic is single threaded
我们的业务逻辑是单线程的
let me show you that
让我告诉你
come on so now if you're going to this
现在就来，如果你要去这个
guy we will see that only one protests
伙计，我们将看到只有一次抗议
are only one threat define it here do
这里只是一个威胁而已
everything right and if we're going to
一切正常，如果我们要
our connection we will see that
我们的联系我们将看到
basically everything happens on the same
基本上所有事情都发生在相同的地方
threat I don't do any kind of
威胁我什么都不做
rescheduling of the actions every scene
重新安排每个场景的动作
is executed on the same threat you don't
在与您不同的威胁下执行
have anything so we got let's just do a
有什么，所以我们让我们做一个
few debugging actions let's just put a
几个调试操作让我们将
few breakpoint here and here and let's
这里和这里的几个断点，让我们
just try to run this guy and to debug it
只是尝试运行这个家伙并对其进行调试
a little bit
一点点
come on buddy do it yeah here we go
来吧伙伴吧，是的，我们走了
start it a little bit of marketing for
开始一点营销
growl in order to run the growl you have
为了运行你的咆哮声
to use just two options all like asked
只使用两个选项都喜欢
me to do that is noisy guy now let's
我要做的就是吵闹的家伙，现在让我们
just try to open our console terminal I
只是尝试打开我们的控制台终端
mean and connect to this guy and here we
意思是并连接到这个家伙，在这里我们
go
走
here we got do unsubscribe so we
在这里，我们要取消订阅，所以我们
accepted the connection and we subscribe
接受连接，我们订阅
it to the stream so we got this don't
它到流，所以我们得到这个不要
subscribe execution at which we just say
订阅执行，我们只是说
we want to listen to be want to read
我们想听就是想读
some data and wake up and as you can see
一些数据并唤醒，如您所见
I'm going to open this a little bit
我要打开一点
broad we are running on default reactive
广泛地说，我们正在使用默认反应式
server one on this on this thread DC
在此线程DC上的服务器一
remember it then let's go for not like
记住它，然后让我们去不喜欢
that but yeah not like that where I am
那是的，是的，不喜欢我在哪里
yeah Here I am now let's try to send
是的，我现在在这里尝试发送
something here we go
我们去的东西
we got another breakpoint and as you can
我们有另一个断点，您可以
see the same the thread is the same do
看到一样的线程是一样的吗
you see it the thread is the same if
你看到它的线程是相同的，如果
you're going to put breakpoint here the
您将在此处放置断点
thread will be the same so basically
线程将基本相同
every execution every data handling will
每次执行每个数据处理都会
be on the same thread so we have to
在同一线程上，所以我们必须
implement some logic which allows us to
实施一些逻辑，使我们能够
to attach our dream to attach our
附加我们的梦想附加我们的梦想
connection to a particular can
与特定罐头的连接
of tread pool or worker for that purpose
为此而设的踏板池或工人
we are going to use scheduler we will
我们将使用调度程序，我们将
create we will use kind of predefined it
创建我们将使用一种预定义的方法
in reactor pal parallel pool of
在反应堆好朋友的并行池中
schedulers or of workers and we will say
调度员或工人，我们会说
okay let's select only one worker from
好吧，我们只选择一名工人
that pool in order to execute everything
该池以便执行所有操作
on executed this worker because
处决了这个工人，因为
execution on in one thread is the most
在一个线程上执行最多
efficient execution that's why we are
高效率的执行力，这就是我们为什么
going to use only one on the one worker
只能在一个工人上使用一个
but it will be different from the from
但这与
the main execution logic so now let's do
主要执行逻辑，所以现在让我们开始
let's use one operator for that purpose
我们为此使用一个运算符
we have to use only publish on operator
我们只需要在操作符上发布
here and we are going to use this
在这里，我们将使用这个
scheduler
调度器
do you see it yeah easy one-liner the
你看到它是不是很容易
same we have to do here because now
同样，我们必须在这里做，因为现在
everything will be on a different threat
一切都会受到不同的威胁
and our varietal diff occations will
我们的品种分化将
happen on the thread main let's say
发生在主线程上
let's name it or on the server main
我们命名它还是在服务器主服务器上
server thread and now we have to execute
服务器线程，现在我们必须执行
every kind of byte writing on the same
各种字节写在同一
thread as attach it to the connection so
螺纹连接到连接所以
we are going to use the same operator
我们将使用相同的运算符
here and now let's just restart our
现在，让我们重新启动
server and ensure that everything is
服务器并确保一切正常
working on a different kind of on a
在另一种上工作
different threads so let's wait a second
不同的线程，所以让我们稍等一下
yeah it started so let's try to connect
是的，它开始了，让我们尝试连接
again here we go here we got our
再次在这里，我们去这里，我们得到了
connection on the main thread and now
现在在主线程上连接
let's try to send some data here we go
让我们尝试在此处发送一些数据
we got another thread do you see
我们还有另一个话题吗
parallel one great so if you're going to
并行一个伟大的，所以如果你要
see whether where the write happens oh
看看写在哪里发生哦
something goes wrong too many
出问题了太多
notifications so let's just remove this
通知，所以我们就删除它
debug point and see yeah it's still
调试点，看看是的还是
working
工作中
so yeah we got echo it works looks good
是的，我们得到了回应，它看起来不错
so let's try to run to run our daughter
所以我们试着去跑我们的女儿
again let's just try to run it and see
再次让我们尝试运行它，看看
whether our application won't be will
我们的应用程序是否会
not be broken after all
毕竟不被打破
so let's take a look whoa something went
让我们来看看哇
wrong just opened a few connections now
错误刚刚打开了几个连接
it's something went wrong this overdose
用药过量出事了
er wait sec no everything goes fine no
er sec sec一切都没有
something went wrong
出问题了
we got overflow so what happened
我们溢出了怎么回事
do you know let me quickly explain
你知道吗让我快速解释一下
what's going on here
这里发生了什么
so because before the egg kind of
所以因为在鸡蛋之前
protests everything on the same fret
抗议一切都在同一根
only one thread were involved in the
只有一个线程参与了
processing kind of the main thread the
主线程的处理方式
mains kind of reactive server won't be
电源类型的反应式服务器将不会
able to you to listen to another kind of
能够让你听另一种
to read and other notifications about
阅读有关的其他通知
key I'm kind of app from the from the
关键，我来自
from the connection that it is it is
从它的连接
ready to send some data it is ready to
准备发送一些准备就绪的数据
send some data and since we do some
发送一些数据，因为我们做了一些
rescheduling which can take a few kind
重新安排可能需要几种
of nanoseconds or a little bit more this
十亿分之一秒或更多
notification will happen will happen
通知将会发生
will happen too frequently so it
会发生得太频繁了
overflow the publish on buffer which is
溢出在缓冲区上发布
used to kind of to store some events and
过去常常用来存储一些事件，
then to read them on the different
然后在不同的地方阅读它们
thread and that's what happened here we
线程，这就是我们在这里发生的事情
just overflow to buy too many
只是溢出购买太多
notifications our queue and we crashed
通知我们的队列，我们​​崩溃了
our execution so in order to avoid it we
我们的执行，所以为了避免它，我们
have to just used one Operator
只需要使用一个操作员
on the pressure latest and it will skip
最新的压力，它将跳过
all redundant or all over float and off
全部冗余或全部浮动
notifications and we'll keep only latest
通知，我们将仅保留最新消息
which is most important to us we don't
对我们来说最重要的是我们不
care about the default of them you just
关心他们的默认设置
need to take one and just read data from
需要采取一个，只是从读取数据
it right you don't need every and by
是的，您不需要所有
using only this one guy we will we will
仅使用这个人，我们将
be able to to survive our app so let's
能够生存下来的我们的应用程序，所以让我们
just start it let's just start it it
刚开始就开始吧
started let's just restart this guy
开始让我们重新启动这个家伙
buddy just restart and it start started
伙伴刚刚重新启动，它开始启动
happening so let's see it works
发生了，所以让我们看看它是否有效
it doesn't except for new connections
除了新的连接
come on buddy
来吧哥们
okay let's just stop everything let's
好吧，让我们停止一切，让我们
use magic world and let's just run it
使用魔术世界，让我们运行它
again in order to make sure that it
再次以确保它
works as expected
按预期工作
wait what's going on come on this
等待发生了什么事
demonstration gods again happened to me
示范神再次发生在我身上
so let me double check whether
让我仔细检查一下
everything is correct come on so that's
一切都正确，来吧
right okay it's running
好吧，它正在运行
that's not good I'm just quickly going
不好，我很快就走了
to going to you to move to the correct
去你去正确的
implementation in tzitzit the same place
在tzitzit的同一地点实施
sorry I have to do that in order to
抱歉，我必须这样做才能
avoid mistakes during the during
避免在期间发生错误
demonstration so let's check ok
演示，让我们检查确定
yeah I have to use here allocate and
是的，我必须在这里使用分配和
let's run it again okay kill Java kill
让我们再次运行它吧好吧，杀死Java
Java again yes it's working it started
Java再次是，它已经开始运作了
and the server ok it's running great I
和服务器好，它运行良好，我
got it so now we can open another one
知道了，现在我们可以打开另一个
connection from our terminal and see
从我们的终端连接，看看
that everything is really working even
甚至一切都在运转
so we got one thousand of OpenID
所以我们得到了一千个OpenID
connection from overdose a server which
从服务器过量连接
just spam spam as spammers and if you
只是将垃圾邮件作为垃圾邮件发送者，如果您
are going to look at the busyness of our
要看我们的忙碌
CPU we will see that the whole CPUs will
CPU，我们将看到整个CPU
be busy by work do you see it it just
忙着工作吗，你看到了吗
started kind of collecting data but it
开始收集数据，但是
kind of obvious that every CPU is
显然每个CPU都是
working for us which is great so now
为我们工作这真是太好了
let's go to yeah another final
我们去另一个决赛
demonstration of back pressure that we
背压的证明
can control but pressure for real and
可以控制，但实际压力
now I'm going to stop that and to
现在我要停止那件事了
demonstrate that back pressure really
证明背压真的
works I'm going to remove this line
作品我要删除这条线
which requests data every new for kind
要求每一种新的数据
of once it get it so I'm going to
一旦得到它，所以我要
restore this guy let's just restarted
恢复此人，让我们重新启动
yeah and now I'm going to reconnect from
是的，现在我要从
my console and we'll send a data here I
我的控制台，我们将在此处发送数据
sent it I got a response but do you see
发送给我，我得到了回应，但你知道吗
it I sent data at some point if you
如果您在某个时候我发送了数据
block it will disallow me to send to
阻止它将禁止我发送给
send data from from the console but in
从控制台发送数据，但在
general I won't get a response because
一般我不会得到回应，因为
my server not request anymore gate and
我的服务器不再请求门和
that's how the back pressure could be
这就是背压可能的样子
control it as well which is cool alright
也控制它，这很酷
let's go back to you to the slides and
让我们回到幻灯片
let's do some summary some final summary
让我们做一些总结
and remind what is this most important
并提醒这是最重要的
here so in order to run everything for
在这里所以为了运行一切
example on the several workers reactor
几个工人反应堆的例子
provides us with schedule a parallel it
为我们提供了并行的时间表
allows basically to run using to run our
基本上允许运行使用
execution to run our stream on the
执行以在
specified on one of the available
在可用的一项上指定
workers and process all the data in that
工作人员并处理其中的所有数据
way like this
这样的方式
only one will be select selected from
只会从中选择一个
the pool of them
他们的游泳池
so to summarize we'll neon still complex
总而言之，我们仍然会霓虹灯复杂
but with size design if you'll be much
但是如果有很多的话，就采用尺寸设计
better it which will simplify our lines
更好，它将简化我们的生产线
live a lot because recta streams is
生活很多，因为直肠流是
designed that for a simplified line up
设计用于简化排队
kind of simplified life when the stream
种简化生活时的流
is natural part of execution right
是执行权的自然组成部分
because you know and connection in
因为你知道和联系
general is a stream another stream so
一般是一个流另一个流所以
this two per did you feed each other
这两个你互相喂食吗
real well finally reactive streams bring
真正的井，最终反应流带来了
back pressure which allows us to control
背压让我们可以控制
of course back pressure on TCP level on
当然在TCP级别上的背压
bytes level unfortunately but this is
不幸的是字节级，但这是
better than nothing and of course using
总比没有好，当然使用
projects reactor you will be able to
项目反应堆，您将能够
write really a beautiful logic finally
最终写出非常漂亮的逻辑
what we have implemented is basically
我们实施的基本上是
what almost happens and the reactor net
几乎会发生什么，反应堆网
is so I have here the main developer of
所以我在这里主要开发
flow of reactor native your latter so
反应堆的本机流量是您的后者
him he will be able to tell you a little
他他将能够告诉你一点
bit more more about internals but in
关于内部的更多信息，但在
general the API is somewhat similar to
一般而言，API有点类似于
that so please just use project reactor
所以请使用项目反应堆
and to learn more about new there is a
并了解更多关于新的
few useful links there is a video from
一些有用的链接，有一个视频来自
henskee boots for whom I inspired to do
我启发去做的henskee靴子
this talk I also to learn more about
这个演讲我也要了解更多
project reactor and to learn more about
项目反应堆并了解更多信息
project reactor nettie just follow those
项目反应堆净值只是跟随那些
links finally you have to go to the next
链接最后，您必须转到下一个
thought which is related to real back
与真实背有关的思想
pressure down on top of any transport
降低运输压力
whatever tcp or i ron and this product
无论是TCP还是I RON，以及此产品
or this technology call it also have you
或这项技术叫你
ever heard about our circuit before so
以前从未听说过我们的赛道
if you haven't
如果没有
about that go to this don't go to ban
关于那去这个不要去禁止
and listen from him about or socket
并听他讲关于
which is designed to bad pressure and
旨在减轻压力和
directive streams between micro-services
微服务之间的指令流
and thank you the source code is
谢谢你的源代码是
available here
在这里可用
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]